锡吕·玛塔吉·涅玛娜·德维女士 Shri Mataji Nirmala Devi
从1970年到她生命中的最后一次呼吸
From 1970 to her last earthly breath
锡吕·玛塔吉·涅玛娜·德维周游世界
Shri Mataji Nirmala Devi travelled the world
去唤醒每一个人内在的灵性力量 昆达里尼
to awaken the spiritual power within every human being called Kundalini.
她四处旅行 遍及90多个国家 接触来自各种背景的求道者
She went to any length to reach seekers from every background in over 90 countries.
有时她甚至自己亲自粘贴海报
Once She even had to put the posters up herself
有时候 她告诉我们 她在对着那些空椅子演讲
and sometimes, she told us, She “talked to empty chairs”.
因她无限的慈悲 她马不停蹄地周游世界
In her infinite compassion She ceaselessly travelled the world,
常常自己支付费用
often at her own expense,
尽其所能给更多的人自觉
to give self-realization to as many people as She could...
从一个城市 到另一个城市
city by city
从一个国家 到另一个国家
country by country,
日复一日
day in and day out,
周复一周
week after week,
月复一月
month after month,
年复一年
year after year.
锡吕·玛塔吉女士给数百万生命带来慈悲 智慧和灵性的恩泽
Shri Mataji brought compassion, wisdom and spiritual grace to millions of lives.
她治愈了很多人
She healed many,
但更珍贵的是 通过唤醒我们内在活生生的能量
but more uniquely, She empowered us to heal ourselves,
她赋予我们治愈自己的力量
by awakening the living energy within
让我们意识到作为世界公民的全部潜能
to realise our full potential as citizens of the world.
在她一生中 我们敬爱的母亲访问了90多个国家
In her lifetime Our Beloved Mother visited more than 90 countries
发表了成千上万的公开演讲
giving thousands and thousands of public programs
这么多人感觉到凉风 获得自觉
So many felt the cool breeze, and got self-realization
成千上万 数以百万的人
hundreds of thousands, millions
她不知疲倦地工作了40多年
She did so tirelessly For over 40 years...